Contact

priyank_1997@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/priyankchokshi (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Financial Analysis
Data Analysis
Research

Languages

English (Full Professional)
Gujarati (Professional Working)

Certifications

Product Management and Development Foundations

Agile at Work: Planning with Agile User Stories

SQL Tips, Tricks, & Techniques

Power BI Essential Training

Managing Up, Down, and Across the Organization

Honors-Awards

Runners Up in the Zonal Round of "The RBI Policy Challange"

Publications

Challenges to Inclusive Growth: Outsourcing Sector in Reverse Globalization Era

How Vijay Mallya Has Been Made Scapegoat

Priyank Chokshi

Financial Data Enthusiast - Technology Enthusiast Old Ahmedabad

Summary

Financial and Economics Researcher with vast experience in Capital Markets. Involved in Capital Markets related data collection and data management. Experienced working with SQL, Excel and other data management tools and large data extraction based on logics. Worked as a Financial Consultant and Individual Researcher for many Individual Clients. Additional skills include Financial Consultancy and Administrative work relating to Exports.

Experience

S&P Global Market Intelligence 2 years 10 months

Data Associate
January 2020 - Present (8 months)

Data Research Analyst - 3 April 2019 - January 2020 (10 months)

Data Research Analyst - 1 November 2017 - March 2019 (1 year 5 months)

Ahmedabad Area, India

Working in the Transaction Department with key responsibilities being to extract, scrutinize and standardize the essential financing related data substantial to the industry of Transactions in terms of capital and equity markets. It includes covering financing transaction data (all publicly announced private placements, public offerings, shelf registrations, equity buybacks, fixed income issuance's, rights offering and credit facilities) from the most active capital markets in the world. In addition involved with key stakeholders sharing insights including suggesting new analytical data points for transaction as a data set. Pro actively communicating product issues and helping out higher stakeholders and the stewardship team in resolving the same.

Family Office Individual Investor

May 2012 - Present (8 years 4 months)

Ahmedabad Area, India

Utkarsh Exim Pvt. Ltd Financial Consultant January 2015 - November 2017 (2 years 11 months) Ahmedabad Area, India

Wealthfirst Portfolio Managers Ltd. Research Intern May 2016 - June 2016 (2 months) Ahmedabad Area, India

Munching Kart
Managing Director
January 2015 - November 2015 (11 months)

Education

SVKM's Narsee Monjee Institute of Management Studies (NMIMS) Bachelor of Business Administration (B.B.A.), Finance, General · (2014 - 2017)

Ahmedabad International School High School, Business/Commerce, General · (2001 - 2014)